export const questions = [
    {
        question: '2 x 1',
        answers: [1, 2, 3],
        correctAnswer: 2
    },
    {
        question: '2 x 2',
        answers: [2, 4, 6],
        correctAnswer: 4
    },
    {
        question: '2 x 3',
        answers: [2, 3, 6],
        correctAnswer: 6
    },
    {
        question: '2 x 4',
        answers: [9, 8, 6],
        correctAnswer: 8
    },
    {
        question: '2 x 6',
        answers: [14, 9, 12],
        correctAnswer: 12
    },
    {
        question: '2 x 7',
        answers: [12, 14, 16],
        correctAnswer: 14
    },
    {
        question: '2 x 8',
        answers: [14, 18, 16],
        correctAnswer: 16
    },
    {
        question: '2 x 9',
        answers: [18, 16, 15],
        correctAnswer: 48
    },
    {
        question: '2 x 10',
        answers: [11, 20, 30],
        correctAnswer: 20
    },
    {
        question: '3 x 1',
        answers: [2, 4, 3],
        correctAnswer: 3
    },
    {
        question: '3 x 2',
        answers: [3, 6, 9],
        correctAnswer: 6
    },
    {
        question: '3 x 3',
        answers: [6, 9, 12],
        correctAnswer: 9
    },
    {
        question: '3 x 4',
        answers: [12, 14, 16],
        correctAnswer: 12
    },
    {
        question: '3 x 5',
        answers: [10, 20, 15],
        correctAnswer: 15
    },
    {
        question: '3 x 6',
        answers: [18, 16, 12],
        correctAnswer: 18
    },
    {
        question: '3 x 7',
        answers: [20, 27, 21],
        correctAnswer: 21 
    },
    {
        question: '3 x 8',
        answers: [20, 22, 24],
        correctAnswer: 24
    },
    {
        question: '3 x 9',
        answers: [21, 26, 27],
        correctAnswer: 27
    },
    {
        question: '3 x 10',
        answers: [30, 32, 31],
        correctAnswer: 30
    },
    {
        question: '4 x 1',
        answers: [1, 4, 8],
        correctAnswer: 4 
    },
    {
        question: '4 x 2',
        answers: [8, 4, 12],
        correctAnswer: 8
    },
    {
        question: '4 x 3',
        answers: [6, 8, 12],
        correctAnswer: 12
    },
    {
        question: '4 x 4',
        answers: [12, 18, 16],
        correctAnswer: 16
    },
    {
        question: '4 x 5',
        answers: [20, 18, 25],
        correctAnswer: 20
    },
    {
        question: '4 x 6',
        answers: [12, 24, 17],
        correctAnswer: 24
    },
    {
        question: '4 x 7',
        answers: [28, 21, 30],
        correctAnswer: 28
    },
    {
        question: '4 x 8',
        answers: [24, 28, 32],
        correctAnswer: 32
    },
    {
        question: '4 x 9',
        answers: [32, 36, 38],
        correctAnswer: 36
    },
    {
        question: '4 x 10',
        answers: [40, 30, 35],
        correctAnswer: 40
    },
    {
        question: '5 x 1',
        answers: [5, 10, 15],
        correctAnswer: 5
    },
    {
        question: '5 x 2',
        answers: [5, 10, 15],
        correctAnswer: 10
    },
    {
        question: '5 x 3',
        answers: [5, 10, 15],
        correctAnswer: 15
    },
    {
        question: '5 x 4',
        answers: [20, 15, 25],
        correctAnswer: 20
    },
    {
        question: '5 x 5',
        answers: [25, 10, 50],
        correctAnswer: 25
    },
    {
        question: '5 x 6',
        answers: [30, 35, 40],
        correctAnswer: 30
    },
    {
        question: '5 x 7',
        answers: [30, 40, 35],
        correctAnswer: 35
    },
    {
        question: '5 x 8',
        answers: [35, 40, 45],
        correctAnswer: 40
    },
    {
        question: '5 x 9',
        answers: [50, 40, 45],
        correctAnswer: 45
    },
    {
        question: '5 x 10',
        answers: [45, 50, 55],
        correctAnswer: 50
    }
]